

UT CODING BOOT CAMP STUDENT FORMER PRODUCTION MANAGER

# MATTHEW OBALLE

## **GET IN CONTACT**

Mobile: 512-971-8374

oballematt@gmail.com

## **PERSONAL PROFILE**

UT Coding Boot Camp student and former production manager with skills in directing and developing individuals in a fast paced, competitive industry. With the transition into web development, I strive to bring my experience as a manager and mesh them with the skills I'm learning at the coding boot camp to become a great and innovative developer

## AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- HTML5
- CSS
- JavaScript ES6
- ¡Query
- NodeJs
- MySql
- MongoDB
- React
- Ajax
- Bootstrap CSS

#### OTHER SKILLS

- · Effective team building
- Excellent communication
- Detail oriented
- · Excellent problem solver
- · Production Management
- Critical thinking

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **AUSTIN EASTCIDERS**

Production Manager – Sep 2017 – 2020 Canning operator – may 2017 – Sep 2017 Kegging operator – Nov 2016 – may 2017 Cellar hand – Apr 2016 – Nov 2016

- Supervise a shift of 8-12 people
- Lead daily meetings with my team to review and assign duties based on daily quotas and ensure we meet GMP standards
- Ensure team Compliance with all company and safety policies and procedures.
- Conduct maintenance on all of our packaging machines and operational tools when needed
- Collaborate with technical and administrative teams to develop and implement packaging plans
- Coordinate with other teams in our warehouse and fermentation departments to ensure we have product ready for packaging and product ready to ship to our vendors
- Work along side technical and administration teams to evaluate production levels, quality standards and maintenance actions to identify and address operational problems and maintain targets
- Communicate with technical team to oversee routine maintenance programs and scheduled service to keep equipment functioning at peak levels
- Assess quality control data with QA managers and Administration teams to monitor and detect issues with quality of final products and improve overall quality management practices
- Conduct End of Shift reports that detail completed packaging numbers and inventory needs
- Complete detailed Downtime report at end of shift to account for any lost production.

#### **EDUCATION HISTORY**

**UT AUSTIN CODING BOOT CAMP** 

Currently Enrolled